Don't follow me.
If we're seen with bandits,
we'll lose all future business.
I'm from Langyue.
I don't belong in the Yun State.
I'm going home.
Really.
I never lie to you.
My Lord,
should we keep following?
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Grand Preceptor,
I'm aware of
your actions.
I am terrified.
I am ignorant and unruly.
Thanks to your protection,
I haven't gone astray.
I merely drank a bit too much.
It's just a scholar's charm.
Not really mischievous.
You're so careful with talents.
You cherish your own and others' children.
You're a role model.
You cherish talents.
I'm just
protecting the treasures of the empire.
Thank you, Lord.
I'm honored but terrified.
My son's misconduct
is my failing.
I humbly request permission
to take him home and discipline him.
Your Majesty,
Cheng Qi is frail
and loves the arts.
He should stay at my residence
to prepare for the upcoming speech contest.
It's a chance to showcase
our nation's talents to foreign lands.
The meeting is not urgent.
Cheng Zhao,
your family has been in military for generations.
It's rare to have a literary talent.
Don't be too harsh on him.
Remember, moderation is key.
Take him back and let him rest.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Since the people of Yun State are plagued by illness,
how about changing the content of the meeting
to praying for blessings?
Your Majesty's consideration for the people
is truly a blessing for the Yun State.
There shouldn't be any sand here.
Something's not right. Hurry into the city.
You lead the way.
Everyone, move quickly.
Yes.
Let's go.
I'm Su Yuejiao from the Su's Escort Agency of Yun State.
I'm heading to Klak City.
Please give me a hand.
My eyelid has been twitching these days.
I'm uneasy.
You know,
if something happens to Jiaojiao,
how do I explain to her parents?
With her strength and skills,
ordinary bandits can't hurt her.
What if the bandits are not ordinary?
What if she insists on "escort her to the end"?
There may be reinforcements.
We should leave now.
I'll stay here
with the escort.
They're gonna take it away.
What if it's fake?
Stand by.
Father,
Cheng Qi was taken away by the palace.
You're good for nothing!
Relying on your little tricks,
causing me trouble, huh?
Don't meddle
in Cheng Qi's business.
Notify all merchants
to check their silver
and send it out as planned.
If there's another mistake,
you won't have to come back.
I know I was wrong.
I'll take care of it right away.
She's just a concubine's daughter.
She's so careless.
Qi Jia is back.
If I don't come back,
I'm afraid you will be mad at her.
Is this little thing
something I can help you with?
Ling Feng comes from a scholarly family.
For the oratorical meeting,
even if he doesn't rely on others to write for him,
he can do very well.
Thanks to Lord Zhang for not despising me.
Since Ling Feng is the head of Xingyun,
I'm willing
to help you.
Can he do it?
He may not be good at
the daily life of the people.
But since the meeting has been changed to pray for the world,
and the Ling family has someone working in the Ministry of Rites,
these eulogies
are easy for him.
I have been influenced by it since childhood.
If I'm not sure,
I wouldn't have volunteered.
When it comes to ceremonial eulogies,
Mr. Ling
is naturally better than Cheng Qi.
In that case,
let's do as Qijia suggested.
Yes.
Get out of here.
Don't make me upset.
[Why hasn't she caught up yet?]
Where's the bandit?
Oh, no.
You tricked us with fake things.
You should be killed.
If you can make us happy,
I'll spare your life.
I'd like to see
who will be the first to lose their life.
Come on!
[Pottery! Pottery!]
[Look at this fine pot I've made!]
[It's perfect for storing grain!]
This leather is suitable.
Make a shawl and have a look.
Look how well this bow is made.
It's very powerful.
Come and have a look.
Coming.
Crown.
Come and have a look.
Newly made crown.
[Come on, have a drink.]
Go on.
It's me. Don't be afraid.
Who are you?
It's me, Bai.
Bai Yanli,
your escort.
Escort?
Where is this place?
This is the City of Diamond.
We were attacked by bandits.
You're injured.
Take it easy.
Say that again.
This is the City of Klare.
Lie down.
Wait for me here.
How long has she been like this?
Over three days.
Based on what you said,
she must have injured her neck.
Then she forced herself to fight,
causing blood to surge upwards,
leading to a concussion.
That's why she can't remember some things,
right?
Will she ever remember?
It's hard to say.
Some things she might recall,
but others she might forget completely.
Make sure she takes her medicine on time.
She's in good physical condition,
so she has a chance to recover.
She's not...
I'll take care of her.
Kneel down!
This is what you've done in Yunjing.
You've become a scoundrel and a drunkard!
Dad, listen to me.
I...
I believed your mother's words
and let you study.
But what's the result?
Look at you now!
You're married, aren't you?
Where's your wife?
She...
You two even dare to trick me together!
What are you looking at?
If you dare to do it, you must admit it.
No, dad, it has nothing to do with her.
It's all my idea.
It's good that you stand up for your wife.
You've made progress.
You did all these
just to protect the Sus?
Dad,
it's all because of Zhang Xi Yun.
She's targeting me.
I can't drag the Escort Agency into this.
Are you blaming me for not being capable?
In the Yunjing City, everyone can bully you.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault that I was too reckless
and got you into trouble.
I used to discipline you
because I was afraid you would be bullied.
Now you know how dangerous the world is.
What are you going to do next?
I...
Of course, I'm going to eat well,
and take good care of myself.
What's that smell on you?
My son is not for you to boss around.
You're really something.
You change your face faster than a book.
Don't forget you owe me three kowtows.
No more waiting.
No more.
Dad.
You... you actually did this for me.
Cheng Qi,
I've never seen
I've never seen him give in.
Thanks to you,
in my lifetime,
I've heard him
say so many soft words.
What are you still talking about?
Go wash yourself clean.
Cheng,
you should have a conscience.
Without me, could you have saved him?
Don't take everything on yourself.
Okay?
It's the emperor
who values Cheng Qi.
The emperor is wise.
Cheng Qi has a new task.
He'll be under my supervision.
Actually,
I've been looking for a chance
to have a drink with you.
In front of the children,
in front of the children.
Come on.
Let's drink.
What?
Jiaojiao is missing?
Then go find her.
Don't worry, sit down first.
I'll leave early tomorrow morning,
so I come to see you.
It's all Cheng Qi's fault.
He hurt Jiaojiao's heart,
So she took such a risk to go to the border town.
Cheng Qi is now in Huayue Tower.
Where is he?
That's more like it.
Cheng Qi.
Who dares to be so rude?
You...
Stop it.
Dad.
This is Su Yuejiao's brother,
Su Yueqi.
So you're the in-law.
Who's your in-law?
Cheng Qi doesn't deserve it.
How can you talk like that?
Your sister-in-law is so filial,
but you, as her brother,
disrespect the elders.
Aren't you siblings?
Jiaojiao's life is uncertain,
he's just worried.
Please forgive him.
Wait.
What happened to her?
You care about her?
You disappeared.
She searched everywhere for you.
But what did you do?
You divorced her at this time.
What kind of man are you?
How can you talk like that?
Dad.
Brother.
I know it's my fault.
You can beat me or scold me.
But can you tell me
what happened to her?
She went to Klak City to escort.
Her team was robbed by bandits.
She is now in danger.
I...
Dad, I'm going to find her.
Go quickly.
Yicheng, go with him.
Remember, if anything happens to your wife,
I won't forgive you.
They've left?
They left early this morning,
heading back to Ning'an with his father.
It doesn't seem like it.
Then what is it? Speak up!
He...
He went to Klak City with the escort agency
to find Su Yuejiao.
♪For a moment of pleasure,♪
♪a lifelong obsession.♪
The doctor said you're almost recovered.
Just rest a few more days,
and I'll take you back to Langyue.
Langyue?
Yes.
You said you're from Langyue.
You remember now?
I...
We're here.
We're the first ones here.
Yes, yes.
There's enough for everyone.
I want one too.
And me.
What are they doing?
Maybe they're also brain-damaged.
They're fighting over Cheng Qi's book.
Who's Cheng Qi?
Don't you remember?
No.
It doesn't matter.
Cheng Qi is ungrateful
and shameless.
It's best to forget him.
Who's cursing Cheng Qi?
Do you want to die?
Why can't I curse him?
Who are you?
You're quite strong,
and have a stubborn streak.
Tie him up and take him back to the mansion.
Yes.
Wait.
You're not from Langyue.
Why are you wearing Langyue's clothes?
It's none of your business.
He's my escort.
You can't take him away.
This is my turf.
I can do whatever I want.
You're unreasonable.
You don't know me?
What's your name?
I'm the head of the Su's Escort Agency,
Su Yuejiao.
Is this your room? Do you like it?
It looks very expensive.
I may not be able to afford it.
Xiangyue Tower is mine.
You can live here as long as you want.
How can I do that?
I'll pay you back after I find the escort.
It's just like the stories.
You know,
your story with Cheng Qi
has spread all over Langyue.
After all that,
who exactly is Cheng Qi?
Why do you always bring him up?
How could you not know?
Cheng Qi is your husband.
Yeah, your husband.
How did you meet?
What do you usually like to do?
What is a matrilocal husband in the Yun State?
Left or right side of the bed?
I really don't know this person.
Why don't you let him go and let him talk?
Cheng Qi is not her husband.
I'd better put it back.
I hit my head.
I can't remember a lot of things.
It's hard to ask him clearly if you don't let him talk.
But you know him.
and you know the escort team was robbed.
I just remembered these days.
You must be badly hurt
and lost your most beloved memories.
You can tell me anything you need.
I'll do my best to help you.
I remember now.
I came to Klak City to deliver goods.
The handover place
is the Xiangyue Tower.
What a coincidence.
Who are you sending it to?
What are you sending?
I need to find out who robbed the escort
and who asked me to send a fake one.
Can you help me?
No problem. Leave it to me.
I also need to help you
get back all the memories
about Cheng Qi.
You're quite tough. I like it.
How could you let that girl get away?
What are you doing?
The person you want to kill is too powerful.
I found someone in the army
and told them there were valuables on the escort wagon.
But it was all stones.
And they were also injured.
Now they're asking me for money.
If I don't give them,
neither of us will live.
You want money before the job is done?
Are you crazy?
No way.
No money.
Fine.
Then give me your life.
I know you always carry gold and jewels.
You have money.
That's not my money.
I can't touch that money.
I'll figure it out.
I don't have any cash on me right now.
Next time,
I'll bring you money.
Fine.
I've prepared it for you.
I.O.U.
Come on, put your fingerprint here.
Remember to bring money with interest next time,
or I'll kill you.
Let's go.
Why do the streets of this city
feel like those in Yunjing?
Yeah, they are.
And Klak City is so big.
How can we find her?
You are full of ideas.
Why are you so quiet?
Where do we go?
Well,
there is a music house called Xiangyue Tower.
I'm going to check it out first.
You're a born gambler.
Go by yourself.
Aren't you going to look for your wife?
I am.
The music house is crowded
and full of information.
Jiao is dressed so specially.
I think someone there might have seen her.
Let's go.
Bro, where are we going?
Follow him.
[It's him.]
Let go.
Are you out of your mind?
How can a woman tear a man's clothes?
Shameless.
You talk too much.
Don't worry, I'm into you.
I won't hurt you.
I don't even know you.
Now you do.
I have someone I like.
I know.
You like her.
but she doesn't like you.
I like you.
Mr. Su
You can live here at ease.
I'll find someone to treat you
and investigate the things you want to know.
Thank you, Miss.
You just come with me.
Baby
Be gentle.
Help me! Help me!
Nice body.
Cheers.
[As the rumors said,]
[this is indeed a replica of Huayue Tower.]
[Be careful.]
Hello.
Sir,
do you want to stay or eat?
I'm here to ask you something.
Have you seen a female escort recently?
Who are you?
I'm her husband.
I have so many customers every day.
I don't remember.
Thank you.
Then help me get a room.
OK.
Thank you.
My Lord,
don't you want to ask others?
That owner was hesitant,
he must have seen her.
Maybe
he knows where she is.
This one.
Yicheng, let's stay here first.
Then we can ask him.
Jiao?
My Lord
My lady, you...
My lady.
In broad daylight,
do you think we don't have anyone here?
I'm talking about you.
Cheng Qi,
do you still have the face to see our boss?
Do you know this person?
Who is he?
I've told you many times.
Frisk them.
Yes.
You'll live here from now on.
Tell me if you need anything.
I don't live here. Let me go.
No way.
My husband can't live outside.
Who's your husband?
Am I familiar with you?
My husband?
So you want to build a relationship first.
I can let you go out.
But
you have to eat with me every day.
You can go out after living here at night.
What if I don't agree?
This is not bargaining.
This is an order.
It's so cute when you are caught out.
You'll fall in love with me soon.